reddirectory.info 2012-06-10

# Red Directory - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy for www.reddirectory.info

At www.reddirectory.info, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us and we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by www.reddirectory.info and how it is used.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other websites, www.reddirectory.info makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.reddirectory.info use cookies to enhance your browsing and shopping experience, store information about visitor preferences, record user-specific information about which pages users access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitors send via their browser. _These cookies are stored on your own computer._

 **Third-Party Cookies**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include _Google Adsense_ , _eBay_ and _Amazon.com_. For more information on our site partners, you may read:

  1. [The Privacy Policy for Google](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). You may opt out of the use of Google's [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html);
  2. [The eBay Partner Network Privacy Policy](https://ebaypartnernetwork.com/PublisherRegPP);
  3. [The Privacy Policy for Amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/gp/redirect.html?ie=UTF8&location=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fhelp%2Fcustomer%2Fdisplay.html%3Fie%3DUTF8%26nodeId%3D468496&tag=bizbytez01&linkCode=ur2&camp=1789&creative=9325).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology for the advertisements and links that appear on www.reddirectory.info, that is sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see and/or in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

www.reddirectory.info has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You are advised to familiarize yourself with the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. The privacy policy of our website, www.reddirectory.info, does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or websites, and therefore take no responsibility in this regard.

 **Disabling Cookies**  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the website where your browser was developed. **However, please note that the online shopping cart at www.reddirectory.info does require the use of cookies to keep track of your purchases and preferences. Disabling cookies for this website will also disable the online shopping cart and impair your online and shopping experience.**

 **Contact**  
If you require more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **contact [at] vyingmedia [dot] com**. If you email us, we use your email address only to communicate with you. We do not collect or use any other personally identifiable information about you. If you contact us, you will not be placed on any mailing list unless you expressly agree to it, and we furthermore do not use, sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you without your consent.

 **Age**  
This site is for use by readers and users older than 13 only. If we inadvertently collect any information of anyone 13 years or younger, it will be deleted upon notification via email at **contact [at] vyingmedia [dot] com.**
